A Guide to the Memorabilia FA437
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Ford Foundation, 10
  - National Equal Justice Library, 1997 September 19; (20" x 13" x 1") wood (Box 11)